https://villaristudios.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the website collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a ‘User’) of the website (“Villari’s”). This privacy policy applies to Villari’s and all products and services offered by the company.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email addresses. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to Villari’s such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use ‘cookies’ to enhance the User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Villari’s may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
·       To personalize user experience
·       We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
·       To improve the custom information, you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
·       To send periodic emails
·       We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Third-party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
The Villari’s has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Connecticut Locations
Enfield    |    Fairfield     |    Glastonbury    |    Mansfield    |    Newington
Simsbury    |    Southington   |    Torrington    |    West Hartford    |    Windsor
FLORIDA Locations
Ormond Beach   |    Palm Coast
Established in 1968, Villari’s Martial Arts Centers are the only authentic source of Shaolin Kempo Karate as taught by Grandmaster Villari himself.
Contact Us
Regional Headquarters:   Villari’s Martial Arts Centers    |    645 Poquonock Ave, Windsor, CT 06095
Privacy Policy
©2020 Villari's Martial Arts Centers of CT. All Rights Reserved.
